(Sheldon:)Mr. D'Onofrio?
It's me, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)They didn't have anything
barber-themed in the gift shop...
(Sheldon:)...so I got you this.
(Sheldon:)Don't know if you can read his little
T- shirt. It says, "Get well beary soon."
(Sheldon:)Trust me, if you were even a little
conscious right now, you'd be laughing.
(Howard:)Anyway...
(Sheldon:)There's new studies that show...
(Sheldon:)...people in comas are aware
of everything going on around them.
(Sheldon:)With that in mind, if you can hear me...
(Sheldon:)...move away from the light
and toward the sound of these scissors.
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)Do you have something
l could use as a cape?
(Nurse:)Oh, dear, did we spit out our pills,
slip out of the ninth floor...
(Nurse:)...and go on a little adventure?
Oh, no, I'm just here
to get my hair cut.